Guide to the Peter Reddaway Samizdat collection, 1950-2010 GRC0002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Mainstream, Circa 1960s to 1990s; Series 4
  - Individual, Series 4 Subseries 4
    - [Wuckert, Konstantin], 1978 July 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - [Pyotr] Yakir + [Viktor] Krasin, 1969 April 2-1984 March 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - [Pyotr] Yakir + [Viktor] Krasin, 1969 April 2-1984 March 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - [Zadrozynski, Edmund], 1980 January 14-1980 March 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - [Zagrabian, Razmik], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - [Zaitsev, Aleksandr], 1979 March 7-1979 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - [Zaks, Valerii], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - [Zalesskii, Aleksei], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - [Zalmanson, Izrael], 1976 February 24-1978 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - [Zamlinskii, Anatolii], 1988 February-1988 April; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - [Zanadvorov, Mikhail], 1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - [Zarins, Alfreds], 1982 March 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - [Zaslavskaia, Tat'iana], 1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - [Zatikian, Stepan], 1979 February 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - [Zaval'niuk, Vladislav], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - [Zavurov, Amnon Amner], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - [Zdorovyi, A.K.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - [Zdriliuk, Petr], 1982 January 15-1982 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - [Zelinskaia, Elena], 1988 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - [Zelinskii, Vladimir], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - [Zheludkov, Sergei], 1977 March 20-1984 February 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - [Zherdev, Sergei], 1980 August 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - [Zherdeva, Nadezhda], 1979 May 6-1984 December 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - [Zhikarev, Mikhail], 1982 February 26-1982 October 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - [Zhipre, Al'gimantas Al'girdas], 1980 February 27-1982 September 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - [Zholkovskaia, Irina], 1977 November 26-1979 July 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - [Zhukauskas, Sh], 1978 July 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - [Zhukov, Dmitrii], 1979 October 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - [Zhvaniia, Vladimir], 1977 March 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - [Zil'berman, David], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - [Zinchenko, Anatolii], 1980 October; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - [Zinchenko, Yury], 1981 November 31-1982 March 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - [Zinets, Mariia], 1979 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - [Zinovev, Aleksandr], 1976 September 14-1985 October 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - [Zinoviev, Viktor], 1989 August 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Zisels [Irena], 1978 November 2-1985 May 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - [Zissels, Joseph], 1980 August 10-1980 October 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - [Ziuganov, Gennadii], 1992 September 27-1992 October 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - [Zograbian, Razmik], 1975-1979; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - [Zolotov, Gennadii], 1980 December-1982 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - [Zomerfel'd, Edgard], 1977 June 12-1977 June 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - [Zosimov, Valentin], 1976 November 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - [Zotov, Mikhail], 1979 December-1982 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - [Zubko, Stanislav], 1980 November-1981 July 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - [Zunshain, Zakhar], 1984 June 30-1985 May 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - [Zverev, Aleksei], 1984 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - [Zverev, Anatolii], 1964; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - [Zviaginyi, Il'ia], 1980 November 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - R. Pimenov "Odin Polit. Protsess" 1968, Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Journal, Series 4 Subseries 5
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [1/11], 1981 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [2/11], 1981 July 14; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [3/11], 1981 March 16; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [4/11], 1980 December 30; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [5/11], 1980 November; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [6/11], 1980 August 3; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [7/11], 1980 April 30; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [8/11], 1979 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [9/11], 1979 November 15; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [10/11], 1979 August 1; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59 [11/11], 1979 March 1; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [1/17], 1978 December 1; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [2/17], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [3/17], 1978 May 14; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [4/17], 1978 March 14; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [5/17], 1977 November 30; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [6/17], 1977 August 15; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [7/17], 1977 May 25; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [8/17], 1977 March 16; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [9/17], 1978 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [10/17], 1978 October 6; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [11/17], 1976 August 3; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [12/17], 1976 May 20; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [13/17], 1976 March 12; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [14/17], 1975 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [15/17], 1975 September 30; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [16/17], 1975 March 31; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - CCE Nos. 33-63 (except for No.36 and no.59) -- continued [17/17], 1974 December 31; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Chronicle Materials [1/3], 1969-1973 March 22; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Chronicle Materials [2/3], 1971 October 30-1973 May 22; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Chronicle Materials [3/3], 1972 September 27-1976 December 17; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Chronicle of Current Events, 1973 July 11-1975 July; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - dvadtsatyi vek, 1-2, 1976-1977; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [1/14], 1989 February 19-1991 September 10; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [2/14], 1991 January 8-1991 September 3; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [3/14], 1992 January 1-1992 December; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [4/14], 1993 October 8-1994 December 30; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [5/14], 1995 January 6-1995 July 14; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [6/14], 1995 July 21-1995 December 29; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [7/14], 1996 January 5-1996 June 21; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [8/14], 1996 June 28-1996 December 20; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [9/14], 1997 January 5-1997 May 23; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [10/14], 1997 May 30-1997 December 20; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [11/14], 1998 January 4-1998 December 28; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [12/14], 1999 February 8-1999 July 12; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [13/14], 1999 July 19-1999 December 27; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Ekhspress Khronika [14/14], 2000 January 29-2000 April 29; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobyti, vyp.28-58; vyp.60-64 [1/6], 1972 December 31-1975 March 31; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobyti, vyp.28-58; vyp.60-64 [2/6], 1975 May 31-1976 October 8; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobyti, vyp.28-58; vyp.60-64 [3/6], 1976 December 31-1977 November 30; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobyti, vyp.28-58; vyp.60-64 [4/6], 1978 March 14-1979 March 1; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobyti, vyp.28-58; vyp.60-64 [5/6], 1979 August 1-1980; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobyti, vyp.28-58; vyp.60-64 [6/6], 1980-1982; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobytii 1-10, 1968 April 30-1970 March 24; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobytii 11-15, 1970 March 1-1970 October 20; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobytii 16-18, 1970 October 31-1971 March 5; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobytii 19-23, 1971 April 30-1972 January 5; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Khronika Tekushchikh Sobytii 24-27, 1972 March 5-1972 October 15; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Khronika tekushchikh sobytii vyp. 1-15, 1968-1970; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Khronika tekushchikh sobytii vyp. 16-27, 1968-1970; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - khronika zashchity prav v sssr, vyp.1-40; vyp.42 [1/5], 1972 November-1974 June; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - khronika zashchity prav v sssr, vyp.1-40; vyp.42 [2/5], 1974 July-1975 November; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - khronika zashchity prav v sssr, vyp.1-40; vyp.42 [3/5], 1975 December-1977 June; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - khronika zashchity prav v sssr, vyp.1-40; vyp.42 [4/5], 1977 July-1979 June; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - khronika zashchity prav v sssr, vyp.1-40; vyp.42 [5/5], 1979 July-1981 June; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Materialy Samizdata - Document numbers 3001-6314 (plus a score prior to 3001), undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - [Prestuplenie I Nakazanie], 1970 December 9-1972 May 16; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - [Samizdat Journal] Poiski, 1978 October 17-1980 October 2; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Samizdat Periodicals, A-F [1/2], 1978 March 17-1989 February 19; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Samizdat Periodicals, A-F [2/2], 1983 April-1988 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - [Seiatel'], 1972 August 12-1973 January; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - sintaksis, 1-8 [1/2], 1978-1979; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - sintaksis, 1-8 [2/2], 1979-1980; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Smoloskyp, v.8, nos.37-40,34; vol.9, no.41, 1987-1989; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 1, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov samizdata - tom 2, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov samizdata - tom 3, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov samizdata - tom 4, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 5, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 6, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 7, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 8, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 9, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 10, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 10b, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 11, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 12, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 13, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 14, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 15, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 16, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 17, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 18, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 19, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 20, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 21, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 21B - Veche Nos.6-9, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 22 - AS 1070-1107, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 23 - AS 1136-1180 incl. "Luch Svobody", undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 24 - AS 1181-1290, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 26 - V.2 of Orthodox Church, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 27 - AS 1300-1389 Religion, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 28 - AS 1501-1599, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 29 - AS 1600-1699, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Sobranie Dokumentov Samizdata - Tom 30 - Helsinki Doc[uments] incl[uding] index!, undated; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - SSSR vnutrennie protivorechiia, vyp 1; vyp. 3-4, 6-21 [1/6], 1981-1983; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - SSSR vnutrennie protivorechiia, vyp 1; vyp. 3-4, 6-21 [2/6], 1984; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - SSSR vnutrennie protivorechiia, vyp 1; vyp. 3-4, 6-21 [3/6], 1985; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - SSSR vnutrennie protivorechiia, vyp 1; vyp. 3-4, 6-21 [4/6], 1986-1987; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - SSSR vnutrennie protivorechiia, vyp 1; vyp. 3-4, 6-21 [5/6], 1987; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - SSSR vnutrennie protivorechiia, vyp 1; vyp. 3-4, 6-21 [6/6], 1988; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Veche, 1973 May 18-1974 April 19; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Vesti iz SSSR [1/3], 1984 November 30-1988 November 15; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Vesti iz SSSR [2/3], 1981 May 15-1984 November 15; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Vesti iz SSSR [3/3], 1980 April 30-1981 April 30; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Isbrannoe, Publitsisticheskaia seriia vyp.1; Sergei Razymnyi, Rasstanovka sil v KRSS I drugie stat'I; V. Nikitin, Chekhoslavatskaia tragediia; Valentin Komarov, Sentiabr' goda, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 23; Khronika Arkhipelaga GULag, Odin god politlageria VC 389/35, Sbornik dokymentov (Vypuski "Khroniki AG" 1,2,3,4), 1976; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe, vyp.30; Svobodnyi profsoiuz trudiashchikhcia, Ustav I drugie dokumenti, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe, vyp.31-32 Rabochnaia Komissiia Po Rassledovaniiu Ispol'zovaniia Psikhiatrii v Politicheskikh Tseliakh, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe, vyp.33; "VRAG VNUTRI" (Sbornik statei) I "V SVETE PREOBRAZHENIIA" (ezhenedl'naia pravoslavnaia gazeta), 1979; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe, vyp.34; SMOT informatsiionnye bulleteni, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe, vyp.35-36; O Sovremennom Polozhenii Russkoi Pravoslavnoi Tserkvi I perspektivakh rekigioznogo vozrozhdeniia Rossii, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokymental'naia seriia vyp. 5; Khronika tekyshchikh sobitii vyp.26; Seiatel' No.1; Seiatel' No.2, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokymental'naia seriia vyp.2; Khronika tekyshchikh sobitii, Vypusk 22; V. Chalikze "Ko mne prishel inostranets"; "Dykhovnoe prozrenie" L'va Krasnopevtseva, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokymental'naia seriia vyp.3; Khronika tekyshchikh sobitii, Vypusk 23; Syd nad Vladimirom Bukovskim, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokymental'naia seriia vyp.4; Khronika tekyshchikh sobitii, Vypusk 24; Khronika tekyshchikh sobytii Vypusk 25, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokymental'naia seriia vyp.6; Khronika teyshchikh sobytii Vypusk 27; Rossiia I Tserkov' segodnia; Tserkov' I vlast'; Bulleten' No. 6 I 7, Soveta rodstvennikov uznikov evangel'skikh khristian-baptistov v SSSR, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokymental'naia seriia vyp.7; Svobodnaia mysl' Vypusk 1; Tri listovki Grazhdanskogo komiteta, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Vol'noe Slovo, Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokymental'naia seriia vyp.8; R.I. Pimenov Odin Politicheskii Protsess, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 13; Svidetel' po sobstvennomu delu I drugie dokumenti, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 14-15; Moe poslednee slovo; Rechi podsydimykh na sydebnykh protsessakh, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 22; Vskhson [Vserossiiskom Sotsial-Khristianskom Soiuze Osvobozhdeniia Naroda], Materialy syda I programma, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - vypusk 24; Soprotivlenie religioznym presledovaniiam, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 25-26; Gruppa Sodeistviia vyppolneniiu Khel'sinkskikh soglashenii v SSSR; dokumenty, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 28; Khristianskii komitet zashchity prov veruiushchikh v SSSR; dokumenty, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 29; Iiun'skie novosti (Zapiski neakkreditovannogo); Mark Popovskii, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 38; ISSN 0343-5245; "Zhenshchina I rossiia"; Komitet zashchity Tat'iany Velikanovoi (informatsionnii bulleten' No.1), 1980; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 39; ISSN 0343-5245; Khristianskii Seminar, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 40; ISSN 0343-5245; Ivan Ruslanov, Zhesn' I Aforizmi Kuz'my Prutkova (vnuka), 1981; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - vypusk 41-42; ISSN 0343-5245; Initzeativnaia Gruppa Zashchity Prav Invalidov v SSSR; Dokumenty, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 43; ISSN 0343-5245; Mikhail Naritsa, Posle Reabilitatsii (Memuary), 1981; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe - Vypusk 44; ISSN 0343-5245; "Nadezhda" Otryvki iz NoNo 2,3,4,5,6, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe, Vypusk 17-18; Iz zhyrnala "Veche" NoNo 7, 8, 9, 10, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe, Vypusk 19; Pytki zakliuchennykh v tiur'makh Gruzii, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe, Dokumental'naia seriia, vypusk 9-10; Dokumenty po delu Leonida Plushcha, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe, Vypusk 20; Iz zhurnala "Zemlia" No.No. 1 I 2, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe, Vypusk 21; Iz-za koliuchei provoloki [tolka odin - god], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokumental'naia seriia, Vypusk 12; M. IA. Makarenko, Iz moei zhizni; Otvet provokatoram, Dopolnenie k kassatzionnoi zhalobe, Verkhovnomu Sudu RSFSR, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokumental'naia seriia, vypusk 9-10; Veche No. 5; Feliks Karelin; Po povodu pis'ma o. Sergiia Zheludkova, A. Solzhenitsynu, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Vol'noe Slovo; Samizdat - Izbrannoe; Dokymental'naia seriia vyp.1; Khronika tekhyshchikh sobitii, Vypusk 21; Memorandum, Demokraticheskogo dvizheniia, Sovetskogo Soiuza, Verkhovnomy sovety SSSR, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Miscellanea, Series 4 Subseries 6
    - C[hronicle of] C[urrent] E[vents] - Orig[inal] Eng[lish] Versions of nos. 1-16 [1/2], 1968 April 17-1969 December; Series 4 Subseries 6 (Box 131, Folder 3)